今天真是玩得太开心了  谢谢
What a wonderful day, thank you.
你开心就好
Oh, we're glad you had fun.
喝了蓝色冰沙  还去了趟容器大卖场
Blue Icees and a trip to The Container Store?
感觉就像我死了
It's like I died
进入了死后脑神经元诱发的幻觉
and went to the post-mortem, neuron-induced hallucination
也就是俗称天堂的地方
commonly mistaken as heaven.
我还是不明白你为什么会买那个药盒
I still don't understand why you bought that pill caddie.
你好好一个年轻人
You're a young man.
莱纳德  年龄是一种心理状态
Age is a state of mind, Leonard.
我这儿已经90岁了
In here I'm 90.
你为什么把你的箱子带去那边
Why are you taking your bins over there?
我就是买来放这边的啊
That's just where I need them.
因为她家衣柜空间不太够
You know, she doesn't have a lot of closet space.
你自己房里的衣柜怎么了
What's wrong with your closet?
亲爱的
Well, honey, you know,
我和莱纳德现在结婚了
now that Leonard and I are married,
我们真的住在一起也合情合理
it kind of makes sense that we actually live together.
原来今天是这么个节奏
So that's all this day was?
先礼后兵  图穷匕见
A plan to butter me up before delivering bad news?
兄弟  别这样
Come on, buddy.
少来这套  我还以为我们是朋友呢
No, I thought we were friends.
你想喝一口我的冰沙
You asked for a sip of my Icee.
如果当时你自己有吸管  我可能就答应了呢
If you had your own straw, I might've said yes.
谢尔顿别这样  我们本来就过意不去了
Sheldon, please, we already feel bad about this.
你知道容器大卖场里没有卖什么吗
You know what they don't sell at The Container Store?
大到可以装下我满心失望的东西
Something large enough to contain my disappointment.
如果世上真的有卖
Although, if anyone did,
那肯定是它们那里
it would be them.
翻译：钢鸟侠赛塔克  小辣椒·猫兹
别扭大菜
谢谢你让我来跟你谈谈心
Thank you for letting me come speak with you.
这有什么
Of course.
鉴于最近我跟佩妮与艾米的关系紧张
As my relationships with Penny and Amy are currently strained,
所以我得转而向你寻求女性的安慰与鼓励
I'm turning to you for female comfort and encouragement.
我很荣幸
I'm honored.
我试着找过我妈
I tried reaching out to my mother,
可是她在上查经班
but she was in Bible study.
莱纳德的母亲在巡回签书途中
Leonard's mother is on a book tour.
我姥姥在睡午觉
My Mee-Maw was taking a nap,
而且一段时间后  Siri的答案开始重复了
and after a while Siri started repeating her answers.
所以我是你的第七选择
So, I'm your seventh choice.
对啊  进入前十了呢  很激动吧
Yeah, I know, top ten, pretty exciting.
我可以帮你什么呢
How can I help you?
在艾米离开我之后
Well, in addition to Amy leaving me,
莱纳德也要搬去跟佩妮同住了
Leonard's moving in with Penny.
我难免会觉得自己被人抛弃
It's difficult not to feel abandoned.
你何不把这个危机看成转机呢
Well, why don't you look at this as an opportunity?
你在莱纳德来之前也有过室友啊
You had other roommates before Leonard.
或许这是你寻找新室友的机会
Maybe this is a chance to find someone new.
或许我可以找到比莱纳德更棒的人
Perhaps I could find someone better than Leonard.
找个让他吃醋咬手绢儿的人
Someone I can rub in his face.
克里斯·帕拉特最近挺火的
Chris Pratt's all the rage right now.
美国男演员  在《银河护卫队》《侏罗纪世界》
这两部炙手可热的电影中都出演了男主角
不知道他能不能接受住进家里小的卧室
I wonder how he'd feel about taking the smaller bedroom.
你知道谁会是完美的室友吗
You know who would be the perfect roommate?
《魔戒》里的甘道夫  可是他抽烟斗
Gandalf, but he's a smoker.
斯图尔特
Stuart.
他已经跟我们同住一阵子了
He's been living with us for a while now.
我相信他也一定很想摆脱我们
I'm sure he'd love to get us out of his hair.
并没有  快乐得不得了
Nope, couldn't be happier.
谢尔顿在找个新...
Well, Sheldon's looking for a...
不要
Nope.
-他会再考虑的  -才不会呢
- He'll think about it. - No I won't!
你看过这本《阿奇漫画》吗
Have you seen this Archie comic?
其实是阿奇大战铁血战士
It's actually Archie versus Predator.
阿奇怎么打得过铁血战士啊
How could Archie defeat Predator?
我也不知道
I don't know.
说不定阿奇的死党其实是终结者
Maybe Jughead's a Terminator.
斯图尔特
Hey, Stuart.
你们俩有认识玩音乐的人吗
Do you guys know any musicians?
怎么了
Why?
我在想如果店里面
I was thinking it might be cool
每周有几天有乐队现场演出
to have live music here a few nights a week.
就是让店里更有
You know, give this place more
"还没倒闭"感一点
of a "staying in business" vibe.
你想要哪一类的音乐
What kind of music are you thinking of?
我什么音乐都喜欢
I like all kinds of music,
但最喜欢的是"免费"那一类
but my favorite genre is free.
我们总说要搞个乐队
Hey, we've always talked about playing together.
这应该挺有意思
Well, it could be fun
搞个美声乐团之类的
to try a little acoustic thing.
我们也可以玩科谣啊
Oh, we could play "filk" music.
那是什么
What's that?
其实这种音乐已存在挺久了
It's been around for years.
就是民谣音乐  但歌曲是科幻/幻想主题
It's like folk music, but with a sci-fi/fantasy theme.
我喜欢
I like it.
听起来就像是
It sounds exactly like something
我不用担心会要花钱的音乐
I shouldn't be expected to pay for.
兄弟  如果要玩这个
Dude, if we do this,
那得取个屌炸天的团名
we're gonna need a cool band name.
其实我心里
You know, I've actually
有个深藏已久的乐队名
had one I've been sitting on for years.
真的吗
Really?
本来是为
It was for this power trio
我初中组的三人摇滚乐队取的
I tried to put together in junior high,
可我当年一缺二
but I was short two friends.
叫什么
What is it?
月球足迹
Footprints on the Moon.
好听得我都起鸡皮[发冷]了
I just got chills.
我也是
So did I.
Me, too.
但也有可能是我得了莱姆病
But I-I might have Lyme Disease.
再签几个名  就大功告成了
Just a few more signatures, and we'll be finished.
这里签首字母缩写  确认已归还钥匙
Initial here to acknowledge that you've returned your key.
好的
Okay.
作为我未来的邻居
As my future neighbor,
我希望你能留一把我家钥匙
I'd like you to have a key.
这里签首字母缩写  确认已拿钥匙
Initial here to acknowledge you received it.
我要给你点赞  你还挺能接受这件事
I'm proud of you. You're taking this really well.
毕竟又不是再也见不到你们俩了
Well, it's not like I'm never going to see you two again.
请看到第23条第C款
Which brings us to article 23 subsection C--
请在这里签名来预留
please check here to reserve your spot
十年后室友团聚会的位子
at the ten year roommate reunion.
我现在就得搞这些吗
Do I really have to do that now?
不用啊  但如果到时你想吃鸡肉
No, but if you want chicken
结果只剩鱼肉  那只能怪你自己了
and get stuck with the fish, that's on you.
好的
All right.
对了  最后
Oh, and lastly,
在这里签首字母来确认
please initial here to confirm
客厅沙发的所有权
that ownership of the living room couch
在此转让给我
is hereby transferred to me
在所有宇宙中永远都是我的
in perpetuity all throughout the universe
以及错列宇宙中也是
and all alternate universes
除了那些虫族母皇下令禁止
except for those universes where owning a couch
拥有沙发的宇宙里
is forbidden by the hive queen.
那种情况下  一切荣耀皆奉献给母皇
In which case, all glory to the hive queen.
好了  最后只剩下
All right, now all that's left
签上名  写上日期
is for us to sign and date the document,
我们就正式解除室友关系了
and we will officially no longer be roommates.
怎么了
What's the matter?
比我想象中困难
It's harder than I thought.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
艹来...
L-e-o-n...
的确"帮"到我了
That helped.
我有个科谣歌曲的点子
So I have an idea for a filk song.
算是
Kind of a,
超级英雄穿越大事记传说的
a power ballad, superhero crossover tale
力量民谣
of epic proportions.
屋里是不是有点冷
Is it cold in here,
我冷[爽]到激凸了
'cause, oh, my.
类似大卫挑战歌利亚这类的故事
Okay, so it's a, it's a David and Goliath story.
就是所谓的人神大战
It's about man against God.
就叫"锤子和鞭子
It's called "Hammer and Whip:
不为人知的秘事之
The Untold Story
雷神索尔大战印第安纳琼斯"
of Thor versus Indiana Jones."
雷神索尔大战印第安纳琼斯
Thor versus Indiana Jones?
你让我的科谣心热血沸腾
You just blew my filking mind.
好啦  我还没创作完整首歌
Okay, I don't have it all worked out yet,
但脑海已经有几句旋律了
but I was thinking something like, um...
♪ 印第 ♪
♪ Oh, Indy ♪
♪ 今天风好大 ♪
♪ The skies are so windy ♪
♪ 空中有飞人  体格赞到爆 ♪
♪ Is that a flying man with a killer bod? ♪
♪ 且慢 ♪
♪ Wait ♪
♪ 原来不是人 ♪
♪ That's no man ♪
♪ 而是北欧神 ♪
♪ It's a Norse god. ♪
相当不错啊
Oh yes, definitely.
等我来一段
Hang on.
♪ 电闪雷鸣 ♪
♪ Thunder clapped  ♪
♪ 只因索尔举起锤子 ♪
♪ as Thor raised his mighty hammer ♪
♪ 印弟饶舌 ♪
♪ Indy rapped, ♪
♪ "好一个屌炸天的神" ♪
♪ "That's one bad mamma-jamma." ♪
接得太棒了
That-that is so good!
是吧
Right?
这词张口就来了
Mamma-jamma just came to me.
副歌是这样
Okay, and here's the hook.
♪ 雷神索尔和博士琼斯 ♪
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩闪电 ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩骨头 ♪
♪ The other plays with bones ♪
♪ 雷神索尔和博士琼斯 ♪
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩闪电 ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩骨头 ♪
♪ The other plays with bones. ♪
老天  这歌屌爆了
Oh, man, that rocks.
还记得《法柜奇兵》第一部吗
Hey, remember The Ark of the Covenant?
怎么了
Yeah?
我们的音乐能把人们的脸熔化成那样
That's how much we're gonna melt people's faces off.
电影中法柜打开后放出光芒
让纳粹脸上的皮肉逐渐溶解脱落
很感谢你对我的公寓感兴趣
I appreciate your interest in the apartment.
我需要循例问几个问题
I just need to ask you a few standard questions.
好的
Sure.
你说你是一位化学家
It says here you're a chemist.
那你觉得元素周期表上的
Which element on the periodic table
哪个元素最被人吹过头
do you feel is too big for its britches?
你是在跟我开玩笑吗
Is that supposed to be a joke?
看来氩元素不是唯一一个
Looks like argon's not the only one
态度有问题的人
with an attitude problem.
通常情况下
In general,
你身上的体味跟现在的体味比
would you say that you smell better, worse
是更好  更糟  还是一样
or the same as you do right now?
我本来想问你
I was going to ask you
最棒的水果是什么
what is the best fruit,
然后我意识到  我想问你的其实是
but then I realized what I want to ask you
为什么你的前臂会贴有创口贴
is why is there a Band-Aid on your forearm,
但后来我又意识到  我最想问你的其实是
but then I realized what I really want to ask you is
麻烦你快走好吗
just can you just go?
你很健康
You're healthy.
你从事科学工作
You have a job in the sciences.
不得不说  如果信用报告结果良好
I've got to say, if this credit report comes back good,
你就是我的第一人选
you're the frontrunner.
我不会当你的室友  谢尔顿
I'm not gonna be your roommate, Sheldon.
可我见了11个人
But I met with 11 people,
最后他们都走了
and they all walked out.
那个好莱坞伪君子克里斯·帕拉特
And that Hollywood phony Chris Pratt
也没有回我推特
never tweeted me back.
我相信你一定会找到合适的人选
I'm sure you'll find somebody else.
希望吧
I suppose.
我到底怎么了  艾米
What happened to me, Amy?
数年前我没有任何情感
Years ago I was completely disengaged from my feelings.
我想说那时的我更快乐
I'd say it was a happier time,
但当时我没有情感  所以谁知道呢
but I was disengaged from my feelings, so who can tell?
我不知道该怎么帮你
I don't know how to help you.
情感是生活的一部分
You know, feelings are a part of life.
过去并非如此
They didn't used to be.
莱纳德  佩妮和你
You and Leonard and Penny,
你们用情感毒害我
you all poisoned me with emotions.
当时的我就像铁皮人  对现状非常满足
I was like the Tin Man, perfectly content
直到邪恶的巫师给了他一颗心
until that evil Wizard gave him a heart.
我觉得《绿野仙踪》的中心思想不是这样
I don't think that was the point of the movie.
好吧  那我就像木偶皮诺曹
Fine, then I was like Pinocchio
却被混蛋老木匠杰佩托变成了一个真正的男孩
before that jerk Geppetto went and made him a real boy.
这话说对了
There you go.
你晚餐想吃什么
So, what are you thinking for dinner?
今晚该吃泰国菜
Well, it's Thai food night.
亲爱的  你不跟谢尔顿住一起了
Well, honey, you don't live with Sheldon anymore.
你想吃什么都行
You can have anything you want.
也对
You're right.
那吃什么
But what?
墨西哥菜吗
Mexican?
意大利菜还是德国菜
Italian? German?
印度菜还是希腊菜
Indian? Greek?
古巴菜还是中国菜
Cuban? Chinese?
披萨还是烤肉
Pizza? Barbecue?
韩国菜还是韩式烤肉
Korean? Korean barbecue?
吃泰国菜怎么样
How about Thai food?
太好了
Oh, thank God
我们要去吃晚餐  你要一起吗
Hey, we're going to dinner. You want to come?
我也想去
Oh, I wish I could,
但我意识到最近我情感太脆弱了
but I realized I've become too emotionally vulnerable,
所以就像一个操作系统
so, like an operating system,
我要把我的人生还原到前一个稳定的版本
I'm restoring my life to the last stable version,
也就是回到2003年我遇到莱纳德的前一天
which was in 2003, the day before I met Leonard.
他的意思是不去
You heard him, no.
等等
Hang on.
你真的认为现在是2003年吗
Wait, you actually think it's 2003?
不啊  我像12年前那样生活
No, just because I'm living my life like it was 12 years ago
并不代表我有妄想症
doesn't mean I'm delusional.
而且既然是2003年
And since it is 2003,
咱俩不认识
I don't know who you are,
所以请快离开这里
so please exit the premises
否则我可要用我时髦的翻盖手机报警了
before I call the police on my stylish new flip phone.
你还好吧
Are you doing okay?
还行
I guess.
我只是有点担心谢尔顿
I'm just, you know, worried about Sheldon.
别担心  他是一个30多岁
Well, come on, he's a grown man in his 30s
假装自己是一个20多岁的成年人
pretending to be a grown man in his 20s.
没事的
He's fine.
但愿吧
I hope so.
不然你能干嘛  搬回去跟他住吗
What else can you do? Move back in with him?
当然不是  我只是觉得内疚
No, of course not. I-I just feel bad.
我也是啊
Well, so do I,
可你不想跟自己老婆住在一起吗
but don't you want to live with your wife
想怎么设恒温器就怎么设
and set the thermostat to whatever you want
还有让你的身体告诉你
and have your body tell you
何时想上厕所了才去
when it's time to go to the bathroom,
而不是每天早上
you know, not a schedule slipped
一张从你门缝塞进来的时间表
underneath your door every morning?
我挺喜欢那上面的天气预报
I did like that he had the weather on it.
相信我  这么做是正确的
Trust me, this is the right thing.
我知道
I know.
而且我们又不是抛弃他
And it's not like we're abandoning him.
再说了
Plus,
我们随时可以视频聊天啊
we can FaceTime him whenever we want,
等他所在的那个宇宙发明了iPhone就行了
you know, once iPhones are invented in his universe.
真不敢相信谢尔顿让你当他的室友
I can't believe Sheldon asked you to be his roommate.
真不敢相信他查我的信用记录
I can't believe he ran my credit.
如果你愿意接纳一个很棒的室友
Hey, if you're open to living with someone great,
我给你一千块把斯尔图特带走
I'll give you $1,000 to take Stuart.
你当时带他回家时
You really should've gone on the Internet
真应该上网查查那种生物
and checked how long that kind of thing lives
能存活多久
before you got one.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我只是以为你的生活
I just thought you might have
可能有个苍白怪胎的洞需要补上
a pasty, weirdo-shaped hole in your life.
我知道谢尔顿为人古怪
Hey, I know Sheldon's quirky,
但他同时聪明又有见解
but he's also brilliant and insightful.
我觉得叫他怪胎不太公平吧
I think calling him a weirdo is a little unfair.
你好  2003年
Hello, 2003!
我们给你打包了泰国菜
Hey, we brought you Thai.
东西都哪去了
Where is everything?
于我来说  是在我的未来
In my present, it's in the future.
于你来说  是在你的卧室
In your present, it's been crammed in the bedroom
我让那位在家具店停车场认识的
by an enterprising young man
有干劲的年轻人全塞进去了
I met in The Home Depot parking lot.
我知道你在干什么
I know what you're doing.
你想引起我们的注意  让我们对你心生内疚
You're trying to get attention so we'll feel bad for you,
但这没有用
but it's not happening.
不  我是在努力搞清
No, what I'm doing is trying to figure out
自己该如何生活  因为大家都离我而去
how to live my life now that everyone is leaving me.
你歇歇吧  我们就住在对门
Will you knock it off? We're across the hall.
用现在孩子们的说法"懒得鸟你"
As the kids are saying today, "Talk to the hand."
现在孩子们不这么说
They're not saying that.
2003年的时候是这么说
They are in 2003.
不  他们真不这么说
No, they're really not.
♪ 雷神索尔和博士琼斯 ♪
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ 一个躲着洛基逃 ♪
♪ One runs from Loki ♪
♪ 一个避着石头跑 ♪
♪ The other runs from stones. ♪
你觉得如何
So, what do you think?
那颗石头其实是颗大滚石
Runs from stones means that-that big boulder,
但是我想不出跟滚石押韵的词
but I couldn't rhyme anything with boulder.
诚实  结实
Colder, shoulder,
钻石  宝石
soldier, folder...
对对对
Right, yeah, right.
但是
But...
你觉得如何
what do you think?
我觉得非常可爱
I think it's very cute.
可爱  这不可爱
Cute? It's not cute.
可爱是形容儿童扮成蔬菜
Cute is children dressed as vegetables.
好吧  不可爱
Okay, fine, it's not cute.
你就实话实说  你不喜欢
Just be honest. You don't like it.
我没有这么说
I didn't say that.
我只是喜欢可以跳舞的音乐
I-I just like music you can dance to.
这首歌也可以跳舞啊
You can dance to this!
♪ 雷神索尔和博士琼斯 ♪
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩闪电 ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩骨头 ♪
♪ The other plays with bones. ♪
我跟你说  哥们  这首歌没动感
I'm telling you, dude, the song has no groove.
不能随着跳舞
You can't dance to it.
谁在乎啊
Who cares?
我还以为月球足迹乐队
I thought the whole point of Footprints on the Moon
主要是写出能让人思考的歌
was to write songs that make people think.
两者皆可顾啊
You can do both,
就像迈克·杰克逊的《比莉·珍》
like Michael Jackson's "Billie Jean."
你会一边跳舞一边思考
While you're dancing you're thinking, like,
"靠  歌词唱的小孩到底是谁的"
"Darn it, whose baby is it?"
你这想法都打哪儿来的
Where's this coming from?
几个小时前  我们都很爱这首歌
A few hours ago, we both loved this song.
我还是爱啊
I still love it.
只是认为它有进步的空间而已
I just think there's room for improvement.
你唱给艾米丽听了  对不对
You played it for Emily, didn't you?
对  那又怎样
Yeah, so what?
你这个妻管严
You are such a wimp.
她不喜欢  你就也不喜欢了
She didn't like it, now you don't like it.
不  只是我这个音乐人在进步
No, no. I'm just evolving as a musician.
而你却停在过去止步不前
You're the one who's stuck in the past.
你说的过去就是一顿午饭前
The past was lunch!
你知道这到底是怎么回事吗
You know what's really happening here?
你的女友在破坏我们的乐队
Your girlfriend is breaking up our band.
这事跟她无关
She has nothing to do with this.
我有我自己的想法
I am my own man.
拜托吧  你的大脑就属于
Oh, please. Your brain belongs
任何一个愿意跟你上床的人
to whoever's willing to sleep with you.
-才不是呢  -真的吗
- That is so not true. - Really?
还记得你差点为了那叫瑞秋的姑娘
Remember when you were gonna get circumcised
去割包皮吗
for Rachel Bernstein?
那个跟瑞秋没关系
That had nothing to do with Rachel.
是我因为包皮被拉链夹到  一时冲动的想法
It was an overreaction to a bad zipper injury.
我受够了
I don't need this.
我要退出乐队
I'm quitting the band!
好  我也退
Fine, I quit, too!
那你就滚出我家
Then get out of my house!
巴不得呢
With pleasure!
拉杰  等等
Raj, wait.
怎么这么久才叫人家
What took you so long?
兄弟  我知道我搬去跟佩妮住
Buddy, I know me moving in with Penny
感觉好像变化很大
feels like a big change,
但其实并没有
but it's not.
你怎么能这么说
How can you say that?
艾米离开了
Amy's gone,
现在你们俩也结婚了
and you two are married now,
你们的离开也只剩时间问题了
so it's only a matter of time before you're gone, too.
好了  你不知道未来会怎么样
Okay, you don't know what's gonna happen.
不  我知道
No, I do.
最终你们会需要更多的空间
Eventually you'll want more space,
然后会搬进一栋房子里
and you'll move into a house,
一起吃晚餐的次数从一周几次
and then instead of dinner a couple of times a week,
变成了一个月几次
it'll only be a couple of times a month,
之后就只有特殊日子才会相聚
and then it'll only be on special occasions,
比如伯纳黛特要跟沃罗威茨离婚
like when Bernadette divorces Wolowitz.
或者比如
Or-or-or like
库萨帕里的诡异女友
when Koothrappali's weird girlfriend
终于讲出把他的尸体埋哪了
admits where she buried his body.
或者艾米的婚礼
Or Amy's wedding,
她嫁给一个比我更好的人
where she's marrying someone better than me.
好吧  听着
Okay, look,
我们不需要操之过急
we don't need to rush into anything.
好吗
All right?
或者莱纳德不用搬去跟我住
Maybe instead of Leonard moving in with me,
我们维持现状就好了
we just leave things the way they are,
就是
and...
有时我们在那边睡
sometimes we'll sleep over there,
有时我们在这边睡
and sometimes we'll sleep over here.
大多数都要在这边
But mostly here.
当然
Sure.
那你在餐厅说的怎么办
W-W-What about what you said in the restaurant?
又不会一直这样
Well, it's not forever.
只是一段时间而已
It's just for a little while.
如果你想  我们也可以把他当成我们的狗
If you want, we can think of him like he's our dog.
可以啊
You can.
你们一回家我就开心
I'm happy when you come home.
我还害怕烟花
And I'm scared of fireworks.
顺便说一下  国庆节都必须在这睡
And by the way, on July Fourth, we're all sleeping here.
好的
Fine.
好的  太好了
All right, great!
给我一分钟时间
Just give me one minute,
我要着手起草新的室友协议了
and I'll get started on a new Roommate Agreement.
好
Yeah.
帕拉特还是没回复  不用担心没位子
Nothing from Pratt. We're good.
♪ 印第的鞭子折断 ♪
♪ Indy' whip snapped ♪
♪ 索尔的锤子砸偏 ♪
♪ Thor's hammer missed ♪
♪ 复仇者对战 ♪
♪ It was Avenger ♪
♪ 考古学家 ♪
♪ Versus archeologist ♪
♪ 印第寸步不让 ♪
♪ Indy held his ground ♪
♪ 还正了正小礼帽 ♪
♪ And straightened his fedora ♪
♪ 索尔说这身挺帅 ♪
♪ Thor said, "That's a nice look ♪
♪ 在1944年的话 ♪
♪ In 1944-a ♪
♪ 雷神索尔和博士琼斯 ♪
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩闪电 ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩骨头 ♪
♪ The other plays with bones. ♪
♪ 雷神索尔和博士琼斯 ♪
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩闪电 ♪
♪ One plays with lightning ♪
♪ 一个喜欢玩骨头 ♪
♪ The other plays with bones. ♪
唱点适合跳舞的好吗
Play something we can dance to.